You killed my brother.
Want to buy a peace amulet?
I see that today,
you will likely suffer a bloody disaster.
Buy my peace amulet,
and it will keep you safe from harm.
Are you looking down on me?
Forget it if you won't buy.
Cut the crap.
I'm here to avenge the Fourth Boss.
Three souls, heed my command.
Spirits, follow my lead.
This guy knows sorcery.
Kill him first.
Step to the Qian gate,
cold blade,
fatal light.
Monster!
I'll fight you to the death!
Master,
I know I was wrong.
Let me go.
There is much gold and silver in my stronghold.
I'll give it all to you.
Aren't you going to avenge your brother?
He pillaged and plundered,
and committed all kinds of evil.
I've long wanted to rid the people of this menace.
Let me go.
I promise,
I will never be a bandit again.
Master.
Fierce fire burns the sky.
Fall.
Qingxuan.
Are you really going to the mortal world?
Leaving the immortal realm,
your 10,000 years of cultivation will be lost,
and everything must start anew.
I was originally a thought,
wandering in chaos
for tens of thousands of years.
Later, I was guided by the Heavenly Dao.
I have been stationed at Sanshanliu
as a deity
for tens of thousands of years.
Now with confusion in my heart,
I must go to the mortal world
to seek the seven emotions
just to find an answer.
I hope the Heavenly Lord
will grant my request.
Your heart is sincere,
and the Heavenly Dao
can help you overcome this tribulation.
I will leave a trace of your immortal root.
If you encounter demons causing trouble,
this sword rainbow
will shine brightly again.
Where the rainbow emerges,
its light shines across the eight directions.
Righteousness fills the air,
and the universe becomes clear.
Keep in mind,
it is your origin.
A single thought of god or Buddha can save all beings.
A single thought of demonic obsession can disrupt the universe.
I hope you can find the answer you seek.
At that time,
you may step into the immortal realm once again.
There's someone over there.
Little brother,
did you stay here all by yourself last night?
Then you're really lucky.
Hurry up and get out of the mountain.
In this mountain,
there are monsters.
Monsters?
What monsters?
I really don't know.
I haven't seen them either.
But they have already eaten a lot of people.
It's said they can take human form.
It's possible
they're hiding among us.
Is it that mysterious?
You better believe it.
I'm telling you, I saw a pile of bones with my own eyes.
They must be the leftovers of the monsters.
What a tragedy.
Little brother,
once you've rested,
hurry out of the mountain.
Let's go.
Master.
Please save our village.
You have such great skills.
Master.
If you are willing to save our village,
I will agree to anything.
Master.
Why should I help you?
Didn't you defeat the bandits?
You must be a great hero.
Since you are a hero,
shouldn't you fight evil?
Fight evil?
What does that have to do with me?
I am just an ordinary medicine seller.
A medicine seller?
What kind of medicine do you sell?
Good luck charms
and wealth pouches.
A peace pendant.
An item to pray for safety.
I have everything you need.
Do you want to buy anything?
Master.
Then what do
all those talismans you mentioned
have to do with
your medicine?
Medicine isn't the only thing that cures illness.
Anything that saves people
is good medicine.
To me,
you don't look like you can afford my goods.
Master.
I may not have money now,
but
if you help us defeat the bandits,
our village will have money.
When that time comes,
I'll buy your goods.
No, no, no.
I mean your medicine.
Is that okay?
No.
Master.
If you don't agree to help me today,
I'll keep pestering you.
This...
That's not necessary.
Master.
Don't go! Let me out!
Don't leave, Master!
Please let me go.
Let me go.
Master!
Is the village you mentioned
far from here?
Not far.
It's just a few miles ahead.
What happened?
Come back with me,
and you'll find out.
Thank you, Master.
Release.
Master.
What is your name?
Master!
Why are you always carrying this bag?
Why are you always carrying this sword?
Master.
That talisman of yours earlier,
how did you do that?
How did I go down with a bang?
Shut up.
Chief.
What are you shouting for?
Save your energy.
I told you to get some food.
Did you get it?
What happened to you?
Did you just crawl out of the dirt?
I'm fine.
I didn't get any food.
But I found a helper.
That master,
he just single-handedly
defeated six or seven bandits.
Feilu,
are you hallucinating from hunger?
This master,
he's really amazing.
I went to a lot of trouble to invite him over.
Let's beg him
to help us fight the bandits.
Look at him.
Does he look like a master?
Look at the people in our village.
They don't even look human anymore.
Forget it.
We just take it
one day at a time.
Oh no! Oh no!
They're here again.
Did you gather
the grain we asked for?
My Lord,
please give us a few more days.
Our village
currently has
no surplus grain left at all.
No?
Then pay with your heads.
Men!
Take away all the women in the village,
except those over 60.
Haihui.
Jie Qianghai.